Nikkei Student Union. Administrative Records. 1984-2001. UARC.0720
UCLA Library Special Collections
Nikkei Student Union. Administrative Records.
1984-2001
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Nikkei Student Union
UARC.0720
8 Linear Feet (8 cartons)
Record Series 720 contains the administrative records of UCLA's Nikkei Student Union.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9947031533606533
Scope and Content
Record Series 720 contains the administrative records of UCLA's Nikkei Student Union. Files include administrative documents; social documents; community, political, and cultural documents; scholarship fund materials; sports materials; volumes of Highlight; and Cultural Night organizational documents.
Please see additional collection guide for item-level description of this collection.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1984-1985. (Box 1)
- Administrative documents., 1985-1986. (Box 1)
- Social documents., 1985-1986. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1985-1986. (Box 1)
- Administrative documents., 1986-1987. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1986-1987. (Box 1)
- Scholarship fund., 1986-1987. (Box 1)
- Social documents., 1986-1987. (Box 1)
- Administrative documents., 1987-1988. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1987-1988. (Box 1)
- Scholarship fund., 1987-1988. (Box 1)
- Social documents., 1987-1988. (Box 1)
- Administrative documents., 1988-1989. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1988-1989. (Box 1)
- Scholarship fund., 1988-1989. (Box 1)
- Social documents., 1988-1989. (Box 1)
- Administrative documents., 1989-1990. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1989-1990. (Box 1)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1989-1990. (Box 2)
- Social documents., 1989-1990. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1990-1991. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1990-1991. (Box 2)
- Social documents., 1990-1991. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1991-1992. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1991-1992. (Box 2)
- Sports., 1991-1992. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1992-1993. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1992-1993. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1993-1994. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1993-1994. (Box 2)
- Social documents., 1993-1994. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1994-1995. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1994-1995. (Box 2)
- Scholarship fund., 1994-1995. (Box 2)
- Social documents., 1994-1995. (Box 2)
- Administrative documents., 1995-1996. (Box 2)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1995-1996. (Box 3)
- Social documents., 1995-1996. (Box 3)
- Administrative documents., 1996-1997. (Box 3)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1996-1997. (Box 3)
- Social documents., 1996-1997. (Box 3)
- Sports., 1996-1997. (Box 3)
- Administrative documents., 1997-1998. (Box 3)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1997-1998. (Box 3)
- Social documents., 1997-1998. (Box 3)
- Administrative documents., 1998-1999. (Box 3)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1998-1999. (Box 3)
- Social documents., 1998-1999. (Box 4)
- Administrative documents., 1999-2000. (Box 4)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 1999-2000. (Box 4)
- Social documents., 1999-2000. (Box 4)
- Administrative documents., 2000-2001. (Box 4)
- Community/political/cultural documents., 2000-2001. (Box 4)
- Social documents., 2000-2001. (Box 4)
- Sports., 2000-2001. (Box 4)
- Alumni., 1992-2001. (Box 4)
- Highlight., 1985-1991. (Box 4)
- Highlight., 1991-2001. (Box 5)
- Cultural Night administrative., 1989-1996. (Box 5)
- Cultural Night administrative., 1997-1999. (Box 6)
- Cultural Night funding proposal., 1987-1988; 1990-1994; 1996-1998. (Box 6)
- Cultural Night funding proposal., 1999. (Box 7)
- Cultural Night publicity., 1986-2000. (Box 7)
- Cultural Night flyer., 1999. (Box 7)
- Cultural Night evaluations., 1991-1999. (Box 7)
- Cultural Night programs., 1986-2001. (Box 7)
- CN scripts., 1987-1991. (Box 7)
- CN scripts., 1992-1994; 1996-1998. (Box 8)